{
    "id": "c5d8854691014edcbd7162743c81f4dc",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Jane cooked dinner …………………………. I watched TV.",
            "description": "We use while to talk about two longer actions that go/went on at the same time.",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "whereas",
                "where as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1b9b5f28c154411ebd1ff56f565bfa05"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t forget to signal ……………………………. turning right.",
            "description": "It is possible to leave out subject + be after when.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "when",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d8921a4c208440e48826b4f3aac39fe0"
        },
        {
            "question": "We have been waiting to hear from you ……………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "all week",
                "all of week",
                "whole week"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "298c05f1c0bb4288a4fd737242d137fc"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am going to the movies. Would you like to …………………………… with me?",
            "description": "We use come to talk about joining a movement of the speaker’s.",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "come",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "07207d9f4aa24ae7b40f62ba2f864c65"
        },
        {
            "question": "Your eyes are just …………………………. mine.",
            "description": "We use the same as to say that people or things are identical.",
            "answers": [
                "same color like",
                "the same color as",
                "same color as"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ee92aa30203142e2a2fd90a2d8d5be5c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The car is running ……………………………… since it had a service.",
            "description": "More smoothly is the comparative form of smoothly. Smooth is an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "smoothlier",
                "more smooth",
                "more smoothly"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "99aa364c17684cf28d6d6c35f4fa6363"
        },
        {
            "question": "I earn as much money as ………………………… does.",
            "description": "We use a subject pronoun before a verb.",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "she",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b8cc8eb14c964f7e8c70edc3fde4c785"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are taller than …………………………",
            "description": "We prefer object pronouns after than.",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "239739fa06314ad58dbf20e3a407c02a"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are ……………………………. your mother than your father.",
            "description": "Like always forms its comparative and superlative forms with more and most.",
            "answers": [
                "liker",
                "more like",
                "more liker"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a3cf3e6b43db487b88f42cfd80c4094e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have given up hope ………………………… them ever again.",
            "description": "When hope is a noun, it is followed by preposition + ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "to see",
                "of seeing",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2f3de79c1fbc4b658363e342f8e641f2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I hope ………………………….. you soon.",
            "description": "When hope is a verb, it is followed by to-infinitive.",
            "answers": [
                "of seeing",
                "seeing",
                "to see"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6b622ac23c464d00b7129ecd83288ca9"
        },
        {
            "question": "People disliked him …………………………… he was arrogant.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "because",
                "hence"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "723b8572436845d7a82d730766c0579f"
        }
    ]
}